<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>TECAA Webpages on Project Documentation</title><link>https://three-strikes.github.io/amethyst/tecaa/</link><description>Recent content in TECAA Webpages on Project Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://three-strikes.github.io/amethyst/tecaa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Setup</title><link>https://three-strikes.github.io/amethyst/tecaa/setup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://three-strikes.github.io/amethyst/tecaa/setup/</guid><description>Introduction # Welcome to the guide on setting up your technical documentation site using Hugo, a fast and flexible static site generator, and the clean and modern Amethyst theme. This comprehensive guide will guide you through the entire process, from installation to content editing, customization, and ultimately deploying your website to the web. About Hugo # Hugo is a popular static site generator written in Go. It boasts lightning-fast build times, minimal dependencies, and a large ecosystem of themes and plugins.</description></item><item><title>Editing content</title><link>https://three-strikes.github.io/amethyst/tecaa/editingcontent/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://three-strikes.github.io/amethyst/tecaa/editingcontent/</guid><description>Overview # In an Amethyst website, every page is also called a note. Each note is controlled by a single Markdown file. To personalize the content of your website, you can add, edit, or delete the respective files.
[!warning]- Do not edit the HTML code
Amethyst runs on top of Hugo, removing the need to know how to operate in HTML to create your static pages. Thus, it is not advisable to edit these files directly.</description></item><item><title>Customization</title><link>https://three-strikes.github.io/amethyst/tecaa/customization/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://three-strikes.github.io/amethyst/tecaa/customization/</guid><description>Personalize your amethyst site # Amethyst offers extensive customization options to tailor your website according to your preferences. You can configure various aspects of your site to achieve the desired look and functionality. The purpose of this page is to enable you to further customize Amethyst and enhance your website&amp;rsquo;s experience effortlessly.
Configuration # Customize every detail: With Amethyst, it&amp;rsquo;s possible to customize your website in a simplified manner.</description></item><item><title>Deploying Amethyst to the Web</title><link>https://three-strikes.github.io/amethyst/tecaa/deployingwebsite/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://three-strikes.github.io/amethyst/tecaa/deployingwebsite/</guid><description>Deploying? # Deploying a website means making it available to the world, by using the Internet. This means that anyone that knows the site address (or URL) can see the notes you published, and includes their content. This is what the page will teach you to do.
This is useful if you want to share these contents with your friends. This theme has been designed to be effortless to deploy, primarily on GitHub pages.</description></item></channel></rss>